<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en-GB"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en-GB" /><updated>2025-07-09T14:48:26+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Heads on Crooked </title><subtitle>Mask on Straight, Heads on Crooked!</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Mushroomification Legs Legs Legs</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025/05/03/mushroom-post-01/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mushroomification Legs Legs Legs" /><published>2025-05-03T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-05-03T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2025/05/03/mushroom-post-01</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025/05/03/mushroom-post-01/"><![CDATA[<div class="title-flex-row">
  <div class="title-main">
    <br /><br />
    <h2>Produce the spores, Spread the spores! </h2>
    <h3>When: 31 July – 5/6 August </h3>
    <h3>Time: 12.50   </h3>
    <h3>Where: The Bottle Room @ Mash House </h3>  
  </div>
  <img src="/assets/mushroomification-fringe1.png" alt="Mushroomification Poster" class="title-side-image" />
</div>

<h3 id="buy-tickets"><a href="https://www.edfringe.com/tickets/whats-on/mushroomification-legs-legs-legs">Buy Tickets</a></h3>

<h3 id="help-us-spread-the-spores"><a href="https://crowdfund.edfringe.com/p/mushroomification-legs-legs-legs">Help us spread the spores</a></h3>

<p>Mushroomification: Legs, Legs, Legs follows the unlikely (and explosive)  collision between a man and a mushroom. In one place, there is a mushroom, deep within the forest, raging against the oppressive mycelial hive mind that it has been born to serve and desperate to create a body of its own so that it might escape. In another, a scientist by the name of Karies is working in secret on developing a human hive-mind with the hopes of saving the world - which in Karies’ mind, means making everyone more like him.</p>

<p>The play explores themes of belonging, loneliness, and what it means to be your own person in a weird slice of history that’s constantly telling us what we should and shouldn’t be. In one world, this might be a story of two lovers finding each other, in another it might be gory body horror. In this world, it sits somewhere in the middle.</p>

<p>Team:</p>

<p>Cast: <br />
The Mushroom – Garrick Pagel <br />
Karies – Till Schindler <br />
Erwin – Tiger Mitchell</p>

<p>Production:</p>

<p>Co-Director/Co-Producer – Lola Rose Wood<br />
Co-Director/Co-Producer – Garrick Pagel<br />
Co-Producer – Leah Byrne <br />
Co-Producer – Till Schindler<br />
Tech – Yashique Chalil<br />
Costume - Tilly Bankes</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Produce the spores, Spread the spores! When: 31 July – 5/6 August Time: 12.50 Where: The Bottle Room @ Mash House Buy Tickets Help us spread the spores Mushroomification: Legs, Legs, Legs follows the unlikely (and explosive) collision between a man and a mushroom. In one place, there is a mushroom, deep within the forest, raging against the oppressive mycelial hive mind that it has been born to serve and desperate to create a body of its own so that it might escape. In another, a scientist by the name of Karies is working in secret on developing a human hive-mind with the hopes of saving the world - which in Karies’ mind, means making everyone more like him. The play explores themes of belonging, loneliness, and what it means to be your own person in a weird slice of history that’s constantly telling us what we should and shouldn’t be. In one world, this might be a story of two lovers finding each other, in another it might be gory body horror. In this world, it sits somewhere in the middle. Team: Cast: The Mushroom – Garrick Pagel Karies – Till Schindler Erwin – Tiger Mitchell Production: Co-Director/Co-Producer – Lola Rose Wood Co-Director/Co-Producer – Garrick Pagel Co-Producer – Leah Byrne Co-Producer – Till Schindler Tech – Yashique Chalil Costume - Tilly Bankes]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/mushroomification-webTile.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/mushroomification-webTile.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>